Manchester Evening Herald Photograph Collection
Vernon Historical Society
- Inventory
  - Republican Headquarters open-Vernon, 10/11/1977; Topics: Politics & Elections (Box 4, Folder MH.626)
  - Three sets of twins-RGH-Rockville, 10/11/1977; Topics: Marriage & Family; Rockville Hospital (Box 4, Folder MH.627)
  - Neighbors Views-Vernon, 10/15/1977; 0 (Box 4, Folder MH.628)
  - Lake Street School Harvest Fair-Vernon, 10/17/1977; Topics: Schools & Education (Box 4, Folder MH.629)
  - Voter registration-Vernon, 10/9/1977; Topics: Politics & Elections (Box 4, Folder MH.630)
  - TriTown Players' "Plaza Suite-Vernon, 10/22/1977; Topics: Entertainment (Box 4, Folder MH.631)
  - Hanglider instructor-Rockville, 10/24/1977; Topics: Recreation (Box 4, Folder MH.632)
  - Daniel Woolwich chairman-Vernon Bd of Ed, 11/??/77; Names: Daniel Woolwich| Topics: Schools & Education (Box 4, Folder MH.633)
  - Nov. 8th Election picture-Vernon, 11/??/77; Topics: Politics & Elections (Box 4, Folder MH.634)
  - Mayor Frank McCoy being sworn in-Vernon, 11/??/77; Names: Frank McCoy| Topics: Politics & Elections (Box 4, Folder MH.635)
  - George Russell Town Planner-Vernon, 11/??/77; Names: George Russell| Topics: Politics & Elections (Box 4, Folder MH.636)
  - Lake Street School PTO Fair-Vernon, 11/2/1977; Topics: Schools & Education (Box 4, Folder MH.637)
  - Live Book Titles Tableau-Lake St School-Vernon, 11/2/1977; Topics: Schools & Education (Box 4, Folder MH.638)
  - Book Fair at Center Rd School, 11/10/1977; Topics: Schools & Education (Box 4, Folder MH.639)
  - Atwood-Rockville High School Vo-Ag-Rockville, 11/23/1977; Topics: Schools & Education (Box 5, Folder MH.640)
  - Rockville Town officials: l to r:Town Atty Wm Breslau,Dir of Adm Stanley Roesler,& Mayor Frank McCoy, 12/??/77; Names: Breslau,Roesler, & McCoy| Topics: Town Government (Box 5, Folder MH.641)
  - Rags Ceramics-ad interior-Vernon, 12/3/1977; Topics: Businesses (Box 5, Folder MH.642)
  - Bernie's TV-Vernon, 12/9/1977; Topics: Businesses (Box 5, Folder MH.643)
  - VCMS Wrestling classes-Vernon, 12/9/1977; Topics: Schools & Education; Recreation (Box 5, Folder MH.644)
  - Lake Street School Hannukah Party-Vernon, 12/10/1977; Topics: Schools & Education; Holidays (Box 5, Folder MH.645)
  - Joggers in Vernon from Coventry-Vernon, 12/12/1977; Topics: Recreation (Box 5, Folder MH.646)
  - Santa at Rockville Library-Rockville, 12/15/1977; Topics: Rockville Library; Holidays (Box 5, Folder MH.647)
  - Rockville High School Toys for Christmas-Rockville, 12/17/1977; Topics: RHS; Holidays (Box 5, Folder MH.648)
  - Jack Walsh, Youth Bureau Director-Vernon, 12/20/1977; Names: Jack Walsh| Topics: Town Government (Box 5, Folder MH.649)
  - Lake Street School Christmas Play-Vernon, 12/23/1977; Topics: Schools & Education; Holidays (Box 5, Folder MH.650)
  - LaPointe picketters-Rockville, 12/23/1977; Topics: Mills and Factories; Labor (Box 5, Folder MH.651)
  - Bernie's-Vernon Circle(one of two unidentified men), 12/24/1977; Topics: Businesses; Vernon Circle (Box 5, Folder MH.652)
  - Skateboard Park indoors-Rt 83-Vernon, 12/31/1977; Topics: Businesses; Recreation (Box 5, Folder MH.653)
  - Beth Phelps (COPE) Vernon, ??/??/78; Names: Beth Phelps (Box 5, Folder MH.654)
  - Gail Slicer-Republican-Vernon, ??/??/78; Names: Gail Slicer| Topics: Politics & Elections (Box 5, Folder MH.655)
  - Zontat "Z" Club-Vernon, ??/??/78; Topics: Social Organizations (Box 5, Folder MH.656)
  - Furniture Gallery-Vernon, ??/??/78; Topics: Businesses (Box 5, Folder MH.657)
  - Mary Frances Coleman-Vernon Jr. Miss-Vernon, ??/??/78; Names: Mary Coleman| Topics: Social Organizations (Box 5, Folder MH.658)
  - Lee Silverstein signs his book at tea at RGH, 1/6/1978; Names: Lee Silverstein| Topics: Rockville Hospital (Box 5, Folder MH.659)
  - Barn fire-Rockville, 1/10/1978; Topics: Fire Dept. (Box 5, Folder MH.660)
  - Flooding-Rt 83-Vernon, 1/26/1978; Topics: Environment (Box 5, Folder MH.661)
  - Talcottville School-Suburban Women's Gives Party., 1/27/1978; Topics: Schools & Education; Social Organizations; Talcottville (Box 5, Folder MH.662)
  - Eric Kusche on Frederick Drive-wet basement and drain problems-Vernon, 1/27/1978; Names: Eric Kusche| Topics: Housing (Box 5, Folder MH.663)
  - Brian McCartney-new RHS Principal-Rockville, 02/??/78; Names: Brian McCartney| Topics: RHS (Box 5, Folder MH.664)
  - Hockanum Valley C.C.-Frier and other man-Vernon, 02/??/78; Names: Frier, ?| Topics: Social Organizations (Box 5, Folder MH.665)
  - Aluminum Recycling Unit-Tri City Plaza-Vernon, 2/15/1978; Topics: Vernon Circle; Environment (Box 5, Folder MH.666)
  - Luau at Rockville Hospital-Rockville, 2/24/1978; Topics: Rockville Hospital; Entertainment (Box 5, Folder MH.667)
  - Building demolished_Mayor Frank McCoy present-Rock., 2/25/1978; Names: Frank McCoy| Topics: Rockville Redevelopment (Box 5, Folder MH.668)
  - Diaamond Showcase-ad-Vernon, 03/??/78; Topics: Businesses (Box 5, Folder MH.669)
  - Coloring eggs at Rockville Library-Rockville, 03/??/78; Topics: Rockville Library; Holidays (Box 5, Folder MH.670)
  - Tri Town Players in "Bus Stop"-Vernon, 03/??/78; Topics: Entertainment (Box 5, Folder MH.671)
  - Students at Sykes School making a quilt-Rockville, 03/??/78; Topics: Schools & Education (Box 5, Folder MH.672)
  - Heart Assoc. Blood Pressure Booth at Product Show-Rock., 03/??/78; Topics: Public Health (Box 5, Folder MH.673)
  - Student Art Show-RPL-Rockville, 03/??/78; Topics: Rockville Library; Arts (Box 5, Folder MH.674)
  - Diamond Showcase manager-ad.-Vernon, 3/3/1978; Topics: Businesses (Box 5, Folder MH.675)
  - Oil truck turns over on Taylor St-Vernon, 3/4/1978; Topics: Fire Dept.; Police Dept. (Box 5, Folder MH.676)
  - Rockville High helps "Pantry Shelf"-Rockville, 3/17/1978; Topics: RHS (Box 5, Folder MH.677)
  - RGH Aux.-Del Hartmann, Gay Vanderosort, Brenda Stocks, & Rita Rasulis-Rockville, 3/17/1978; Names: Hartmann, Vanderosort, Rasulis, Stocks| Topics: Rockville Hospital (Box 5, Folder MH.678)
  - Alan Natisisky's goat has triplets-Vernon, 3/23/1978; Names: Alan Natisisky| Topics: Farming (Box 5, Folder MH.679)
  - Rabbit Road Race runners start)-Rockville, 3/27/1978; Topics: Recreation (Box 5, Folder MH.680)
  - Rabbit Road Race (Rabbit at Finish Line)-Rockville, 3/27/1978; Topics: Recreation (Box 5, Folder MH.681)
  - Randy Sanborn, Brett Larsh, Jeff Vale at RPL-Rockville, 04/??/78; Names: Randy Sanborn, Brett Larsh, Jeff Vale| Topics: Rockville Library (Box 5, Folder MH.682)
  - Center Road School Operetta-Vernon, 4/6/1978; Topics: Schools & Education (Box 5, Folder MH.683)
  - Miss Vernon Contest-Vernon, 4/8/1978; Topics: Social Organizations (Box 5, Folder MH.684)
  - Valley Falls Park-Fishing Derby-Vernon, 4/17/1978; Topics: Recreation; Parks (Box 5, Folder MH.685)
  - Anthony Patrizz, Jr. & Michael Polo Rockville Fireman & Model truck-Rockville, 4/18/1978; Names: Anthony Patrizz & Michale Polo| Topics: Fire Dept. (Box 5, Folder MH.686)
  - Marie Herbst-Vernon, 05/??/78; Names: Marie Herbst| Topics: Politics & Elections (Box 5, Folder MH.687)
  - Maple Street School-seed planting-Rockville, 05/??/78; Topics: Schools & Education (Box 5, Folder MH.688)
  - Mrs. Glenn Reams-Vernon, 05???/78; Names: Mrs. Glenn Reams (Box 5, Folder MH.689)
  - Center Road School Bike Hike-Vernon, 5/1/1978; Topics: Schools & Education; Recreation (Box 5, Folder MH.690)
  - High school students paint and clean RHS-Rockville, 5/1/1978; Topics: Schools & Education (Box 5, Folder MH.691)
  - Bloodmobile visits RHS-Rockville, 5/5/1978; Topics: Schools & Education (Box 5, Folder MH.692)
  - Health Fair at RHG-Rockville, 5/8/1978; Topics: Rockville Hospital; Public Health (Box 5, Folder MH.693)
  - Tri City Plaza-Tolland County Art Show-Vernon, 5/8/1978; Topics: Vernon Circle; Arts (Box 5, Folder MH.694)
  - Alpine Haus remodeling-Vernon, 5/11/1978; Topics: Businesses (Box 5, Folder MH.695)
  - Rockville Hospital Ground Breaking-Rockville, 5/18/1978; Topics: Rockville Hospital (Box 5, Folder MH.696)
  - RHS Service Club dinner for senior citizens-Rockville, 5/18/1978; Topics: RHS; Senior Citizens (Box 5, Folder MH.697)
  - Brian McCartney- RHS Principal-Rockville, 5/24/1978; Names: Brian McCartney| Topics: RHS (Box 5, Folder MH.698)
  - Roseann Kapsia and Debbie Rich -Vernon, 06/??/78; Names: Roseann Kapsia & Debbie Rich (Box 5, Folder MH.699)
  - Dr. R. Ramsdell & Dr. B. Sidman(Ramsdell retirement)-Vernon, 06/??/78; Names: Raymond Ramsdell & B. Sidman| Topics: Schools & Education (Box 5, Folder MH.700)
  - Dr. Paul Hofsess-Vernon, 06/??/78; Names: Paul Hofsess (Box 5, Folder MH.701)
  - Center Road School Circus-Vernon, 06/??/78; Topics: Schools & Education (Box 5, Folder MH.702)
  - Kids Town Rockville Vo-Ag-Rockville, 6/2/1978; Topics: RHS (Box 5, Folder MH.703)
  - Dot Magnunson honored by Lake St School children-Vernon, 6/9/1978; Names: Dot Magnunson| Topics: Schools & Education (Box 5, Folder MH.704)
  - Kids Festival at Hockanum Day Care Ctr-Rockville, 6/12/1978; Topics: Schools & Education (Box 5, Folder MH.705)
  - Calvin J. Rutt, Talcottville Rd-Vernon, 6/14/1978; Names: Calvin J. Rutt (Box 5, Folder MH.706)
  - Lake St School play "Good Old 1890s"-Vernon, 6/14/1978; Topics: Schools & Education (Box 5, Folder MH.707)
  - RHS honored by Governor-Rockville, 6/16/1978; Topics: Schools & Education (Box 5, Folder MH.708)
  - High School Graduation-Rockville, 6/22/1978; Topics: Schools & Education (Box 5, Folder MH.709)
  - Gerber Farm Tour-Vernon, 07/??/78; Topics: Businesses; Farming (Box 5, Folder MH.710)
  - Swimmer at Vernon El Pool-Vernon, 07/??/78; Topics: Recreation (Box 5, Folder MH.711)
  - Dr. Bernard Sidman-Vernon, 07/??/78; Names: Bernard Sidman (Box 5, Folder MH.712)
  - Lydia Perry-Vernon, 07/??/78; Names: Lydia Perry (Box 5, Folder MH.713)
  - Pets at Rockville Library-Rockville, 7/12/1978; Topics: Rockville Library (Box 5, Folder MH.714)
  - Mayor passing out popsicles at Henry Park (Frank McCoy)-Rockville, 7/14/1978; Names: Frank McCoy| Topics: Politics & Elections; Parks (Box 5, Folder MH.715)
  - Field Day at Henry Park-Rockville, 7/22/1978; Topics: Recreation; Parks (Box 5, Folder MH.716)
  - Swimming class-Vernon, 7/24/1978; Topics: Businesses (Box 5, Folder MH.717)
  - Hearing on liquor Ordinance-Vernon, 08/??/78; Topics: Town Government (Box 5, Folder MH.718)
  - Kids drive in Safety Town-Vernon, 8/12/1978; Topics: Schools & Education (Box 5, Folder MH.719)
  - Ronald J. Ostafin-Vernon, 8/16/1978; Names: Ronald J. Ostafin (Box 5, Folder MH.720)
  - Thomas H. Dooley-Vernon, 8/24/1978; Names: Thomas Dooley (Box 5, Folder MH.721)
  - Elizabeth L. Gessay-Rockville, 8/24/1978; Names: Elizabeth L. Gessay (Box 5, Folder MH.722)
  - Hortonsphere (now removed)-Vernon, 09/??/78; Topics: Businesses (Box 5, Folder MH.723)
  - Vicky Kosakowski manager-Worth's-Vernon, 10/??/78; Names: Vicky Kosakowski| Topics: Businesses (Box 5, Folder MH.724)
  - Cory Kupferschmid & Glen Schlude in Agway Car-Vernon, 10/??/78; Names: Cory Kupferschmid & Glen Schlude (Box 5, Folder MH.725)
  - Thomas J. Wolfe-Vernon, 10/15/1978; Names: Thomas J. Wolfe (Box 5, Folder MH.726)
  - Ed Jordan's Carpets Ad-Vernon, 10/23/1978; Topics: Businesses (Box 5, Folder MH.727)
  - Homecraft Building Ad(Exterior & interior)Vernon, 10/25/1978; Topics: Businesses (Box 5, Folder MH.728)
  - Robert Dotson, Dir. Of Admin-Vernon, 12/??/78; Names: Robert Dotson| Topics: Town Government (Box 5, Folder MH.729)
  - Rockville Hospital Maternity Ward-Rockville, ??/??/79; Topics: Rockville Hospital (Box 5, Folder MH.730)
  - Jack Walsh-Karate-Vernon, ??/??/79; Names: Jack Walsh| Topics: Businesses (Box 5, Folder MH.731)
  - Marie Herbst sworn in as Mayor-Vernon, ??/??/79; Names: Marie Herbst| Topics: Politics & Elections (Box 5, Folder MH.732)
  - Stephen Diana-Vernon, ??/??/79; Names: Stephen Diana (Box 5, Folder MH.733)
  - Scenes near Phoenix Street (Phoenix mill dam)-Vernon, ??/??/79; Topics: Landmarks (Box 5, Folder MH.734)
  - Congregational Church-Hungarian supper-Talcottville, ??/??/79; Topics: Churches; Talcottville (Box 5, Folder MH.735)
  - Vo-Ag Photos (Jessica Lawrence), ??/??/79; Topics: RHS (Box 5, Folder MH.736)
  - Candidates-Vernon, ??/??/79; Topics: Politics & Elections (Box 5, Folder MH.737)
  - Nick Carbone and Lester Baum-Vernon, ??/??/79; Names: Lester Baum & Nick Carbone (Box 5, Folder MH.738)
  - Paul Eno-Chimney Sweep-Vernon, 01/??/79; Names: Paul Eno| Topics: Businesses (Box 5, Folder MH.739)
  - Sacred Heart Church-Vernon, 1/3/1979; Topics: Churches (Box 5, Folder MH.740)
  - Congregational Church-Talcottville, 1/15/1979; Topics: Churches; Talcottville (Box 5, Folder MH.741)
  - Welles Village-Talcottville, 1/15/1979; Topics: Senior Citizens (Box 5, Folder MH.742)
  - Courthouse Fire-Rockville, 1/24/1979; Topics: Fire Dept.; Law and Lawyers (Box 5, Folder MH.743)
  - Flooding-Vernon, 1/26/1979; Topics: Environment (Box 5, Folder MH.744)
  - Fitch Block-Union Street-Rockville, 02/??/79; Topics: Landmarks (Box 5, Folder MH.745)
  - Hartford Nat Bank Building-Elm St-Rockville, 02/??/79; Topics: Landmarks (Box 5, Folder MH.746)
  - Blonstein Fire-Vernon, 02/??/79; Topics: Fire Dept. (Box 5, Folder MH.747)
  - Elementary School dance class-Vernon, 2/17/1979; Topics: Schools & Education (Box 5, Folder MH.748)
  - John F. Perry of LaBonne Agency-Vernon, 2/7/1979; Names: John F. Perry (Box 5, Folder MH.749)
  - Show at Talcottville School by RHS-Talcottville, 2/19/1979; Topics: Schools & Education; RHS (Box 5, Folder MH.750)
  - Balloons at Lake Street School-Vernon, 03/??/79; Topics: Schools & Education (Box 5, Folder MH.751)
  - Marie and Paul Herbst-Vernon, 03/??/79; Names: Marie & Paul Herbst (Box 5, Folder MH.752)
  - Art Workshop-Vernon, 03/??/79; Topics: Recreation; Arts (Box 5, Folder MH.753)
  - Hospital Construction-Rockville, 03/??/79; Topics: Rockville Hospital (Box 5, Folder MH.754)
  - Tri Town Players in "Look Homeward, Angel"-Rockville, 3/21/1979; Topics: Entertainment (Box 5, Folder MH.755)
  - Open house & craft show at RHS Vo-Ag Program-Rockville, 3/31/1979; Topics: RHS (Box 5, Folder MH.756)
  - Father John J. White-St. Bernard's-Rockville, 04/??/79; Names: Father John White| Topics: Churches (Box 5, Folder MH.757)
  - Fashion modeling at the Middle School-Vernon, 4/5/1979; Topics: Schools & Education; Entertainment (Box 5, Folder MH.758)
  - Fishing Fly demonstration at A&B Sports Shop-Vernon, 4/7/1979; Topics: Businesses; Recreation (Box 5, Folder MH.759)
  - Clown Town Promotion-Vernon, 4/18/1979; Topics: Entertainment (Box 5, Folder MH.760)
  - Miss Vernon Pagent-Vernon, 4/23/1979; Topics: Civic Organizations (Box 5, Folder MH.761)
  - Thomas Wolff, Vernon, 4/24/1979; Names: Thomas Wolff (Box 5, Folder MH.762)
  - Rockville High Drama Club scene-Rockville, 4/27/1979; Topics: RHS; Entertainment (Box 5, Folder MH.763)
  - Welles Village-Parking lot damage-Talcottville, 4/30/1979; Topics: Talcottville; Environment (Box 5, Folder MH.764)
  - Jonathan Connell Valedictorian-RHS-Rockville, 05/??/79; Names: Jonathan Connell| Topics: Schools & Education (Box 5, Folder MH.765)
  - Linda Strnad & Jorge Roccotaliata-RHS, 05/??/79; Names: Linda Strnad & Jorge Roccotaliata| Topics: RHS (Box 5, Folder MH.766)
  - Hackanum Valley Day Care-May Day Party-Vernon, 5/2/1979; Topics: Schools & Education (Box 5, Folder MH.767)
  - Special Olympics at Rockville High-Rockville, 5/12/1979; Topics: RHS; Social Organizations (Box 5, Folder MH.768)
  - Fun Day at an elementary school-Vernon, 5/12/1979; Topics: Schools & Education (Box 5, Folder MH.769)
  - Donald G. Pardus V.P. Eastern Utilities Assoc.-Vernon, 5/19/1979; Names: Donald G. Pardus (Box 5, Folder MH.770)
  - Talcottville School Graduation-Talcottville, 06/??/79; Topics: Schools & Education; Talcottville (Box 5, Folder MH.771)
  - Z meeting at Rockville High-Rockville, 06?//?79; Topics: RHS; Social Organizations (Box 5, Folder MH.772)
  - Jeorge Roccotoliata-Vernon, 06/??/79; Names: Jeorge Roccotoliata (Box 5, Folder MH.773)
  - RGH opens Physical Therapy Unit-Rockville, 06/??/79; Topics: Rockville Hospital (Box 5, Folder MH.774)
  - Jonathan Connell Valedictorian-RHS-Rockville, 06/??/79; Names: Jonathan Connell| Topics: RHS (Box 5, Folder MH.775)
  - YMCA Awards for Volunteers-Vernon, 06/??/79; Topics: Civic Organizations (Box 5, Folder MH.776)
  - Aluminum recycling-Vernon, 6/7/1979; Topics: Environment (Box 5, Folder MH.777)
  - Fireman's picnic for Talcottville School children-Talcottville, 6/12/1979; Topics: Schools & Education; Fire Dept. (Box 5, Folder MH.778)
  - Vernon Arts Council Fair with Peace Train-Vernon, 6/16/1979; Topics: Entertainment; Arts (Box 5, Folder MH.779)
  - Faye Lee Hill-Rainbow Girls-Rockville, 6/16/1979; Names: Faye Lee Hill| Topics: Social Organizations (Box 5, Folder MH.780)
  - Walter A Daniels, Jr.-Vernon, 6/22/1979; Names: Walter A. Daniels (Box 5, Folder MH.781)
  - Rockville Hospital Junior Volunteers Receive hats-Rockville, 6/27/1979; Topics: Rockville Hospital (Box 5, Folder MH.782)
  - Middle School play-Vernon, 7/17/1979; Topics: Schools & Education (Box 5, Folder MH.783)
  - Two sets of twins-Vernon, 7/25/1979; Topics: Marriage & Family (Box 5, Folder MH.784)
  - Safety Town-Vernon, 7/28/1979; Topics: Schools & Education (Box 5, Folder MH.785)
  - Mechanic at Police Station-Vernon, 08/??/79; Topics: Police Dept. (Box 5, Folder MH.786)
  - Christine Merrithew-promotion-Rockville Bank-Rockville, 8/1/1979; Names: Christine Merrithew| Topics: Businesses (Box 5, Folder MH.787)
  - Band at Henry Park-Rockville, 8/16/1979; Topics: Entertainment; Parks (Box 5, Folder MH.788)
  - Maureen C. Curry of Vernon Nat. Bank-Vernon, 8/27/1979; Names: Maureen C. Curry| Topics: Businesses (Box 5, Folder MH.789)
  - Fire at Union Church, 8/30/1979; Topics: Fire Dept.; Churches (Box 5, Folder MH.790)
  - Two children in new hospital pediatrics ward-Rockville, 09/??/79; Topics: Rockville Hospital (Box 5, Folder MH.791)
  - Vo-Ag-Vernon, 09/??/79; Topics: RHS (Box 5, Folder MH.792)
  - Tennis instruction at high school-Rockville, 9/11/1979; Topics: RHS; Recreation (Box 5, Folder MH.793)
  - Better Bedding-ad-Vernon, 9/12/1979; Topics: Businesses (Box 5, Folder MH.794)
  - Camera Kingdom ad-Vernon, 9/13/1979; Topics: Businesses (Box 5, Folder MH.795)
  - Hospital landscaping-Rockville, 10/??/79; Topics: Rockville Hospital (Box 5, Folder MH.796)
  - Mayor Frank McCoy & others at mini park-Rockville, 10/??/79; Names: Frank McCoy| Topics: Parks (Box 5, Folder MH.797)
  - Sykes School teacher bakes cake-Rockville, 10/18/1979; Topics: Schools & Education (Box 5, Folder MH.798)
  - John O'Connell-Vernon, 10/22/1979; Names: John O'Connell (Box 5, Folder MH.799)
  - The Curious Savage play at Middle School-Vernon, 10/29/1979; Topics: Schools & Education; Entertainment (Box 6, Folder MH.800)
  - Haunted house at Vernon Fire Dept.-Vernon, 10/29/1979; Topics: Fire Dept.; Entertainment (Box 6, Folder MH.801)
  - Pritchard Block Fire-Rockville, 11/??/79; Topics: Fire Dept. (Box 6, Folder MH.802)
  - Democratic Headquarters-Vernon, 11/6/1979; 0 (Box 6, Folder MH.803)
  - Lake Street School students baking-Vernon, 11/6/1979; Topics: Schools & Education; Politics & Elections (Box 6, Folder MH.804)
  - Robert T. Crowley-Vernon, 11/15/1979; Names: Robert t. Crowley (Box 6, Folder MH.805)
  - William R. Rylander-Vernon, 11/19/1979; Names: William R. Rylander (Box 6, Folder MH.806)
  - Lake Street School students making Christmas ornaments-Vernon, 12/??/79; Topics: Schools & Education (Box 6, Folder MH.807)
  - Antique Show-Vernon, 12/3/1979; Topics: Arts (Box 6, Folder MH.808)
  - Suburban Women's Club-mittens & money tree-Vernon, 12/5/1979; Topics: Social Organizations (Box 6, Folder MH.809)
  - VCMS students write letters-Vernon, 12/8/1979; Topics: Schools & Education (Box 6, Folder MH.810)
  - Bridal Store-ad.-Vernon, 12/12/1979; Topics: Businesses (Box 6, Folder MH.811)
  - Factory shoe mart at Vernon Circle-Vernon, 12/??/79; Topics: Businesses; Vernon Circle (Box 6, Folder MH.812)
  - Lake Street School-Hannukah Party-Vernon, 12/18/1979; Topics: Schools & Education; Holidays (Box 6, Folder MH.813)
  - 1st Luth Church choir sings carols at Vernon Grange-Vernon, 12/22/1979; Topics: Churches; Farming (Box 6, Folder MH.814)
  - Pediatrics Dept-Christmas tree-Rockville, 12/22/1979; Topics: Rockville Hospital; Holidays (Box 6, Folder MH.815)
  - Baby going home from Hospital in Xmas stocking-Rockville, 12/22/1979; Topics: Rockville Hospital; Holidays (Box 6, Folder MH.816)
  - Jack Beatte-Vernon, ??/??/80; Names: Jack Beatte (Box 6, Folder MH.817)
  - Stage Coach Restaaurant-Rt 83-Vernon, ??/??/80; Topics: Businesses (Box 6, Folder MH.818)
  - Father John White and Miss?-Rockville, ??/??/80; Names: Father John White| Topics: Social Organizations; Churches (Box 6, Folder MH.819)
  - Middle School Choir rehearsal-Vernon, ??/??/80; Topics: Schools & Education (Box 6, Folder MH.820)
  - People at Valley Falls Park-Vernon, ??/??/80; Topics: Recreation; Parks; Environment (Box 6, Folder MH.821)
  - Playscape at Maple Street School-Rockville, ??/??/80; Topics: Schools & Education (Box 6, Folder MH.822)
  - Roman Feast at Sykes School-Rockville, 01/??/80; Topics: Schools & Education (Box 6, Folder MH.823)
  - Award to Vernon Elementary School-Vernon, 1/9/1980; Topics: Schools & Education (Box 6, Folder MH.824)
  - Tom Hewitt-Vernon, 1/23/1980; Names: Tom Hewitt (Box 6, Folder MH.825)
  - Creative Movement class at Henry Park-Rockville, 1/24/1980; Topics: Recreation; Parks (Box 6, Folder MH.826)
  - Amerbelle Mill Complex-Rockville, 02/??/80; Topics: Businesses; Mills and Factories (Box 6, Folder MH.827)
  - Roosevelt Mills-Rockville, 02/??/80; Topics: Businesses; Mills and Factories (Box 6, Folder MH.828)
  - Snake program at Vernon El School-Vernon, 2/2/1980; Topics: Schools & Education (Box 6, Folder MH.829)
  - Byrl N. Boyce Heritage S&L Direstor-Vernon, 2/11/1980; Names: Byrl N. Boyce| Topics: Businesses (Box 6, Folder MH.830)
  - Charles Sullivan, Jr.-Vernon, 2/11/1980; Names: Charles Sullivan, Jr. (Box 6, Folder MH.831)
  - Bruce A. Wilson Colonial Bank-Vernon, 2/27/1980; Names: Bruce A, Wilson (Box 6, Folder MH.832)
  - Kjellquist-Vernon Police Dept.-Vernon, 03/??/80; Names: Kjellquist| Topics: Police Dept. (Box 6, Folder MH.833)
  - Balloons at Vernon Elementary School-Vernon, 03/??/80; Topics: Schools & Education (Box 6, Folder MH.834)
  - Baum & Harlow-Vernon, 03/???80; Names: Baum & Harlow (Box 6, Folder MH.835)
  - Board of Ed-Superintendents & Brisson-Vernon, 03???/80; Names: Brisson| Topics: Schools & Education (Box 6, Folder MH.836)
  - Chip Carter & others at Lester Baum's House-Rockville, 03/??/80; Names: Carter & Baum (Box 6, Folder MH.837)
  - Tearing down the Pritchard Block-Rockville, 03/??/80; Topics: Housing; Rockville Redevelopment; Landmarks (Box 6, Folder MH.838)
  - Gym program at Maple Street School-Rockville, 03/??/80; Topics: Schools & Education (Box 6, Folder MH.839)
  - Scenes from Mayor's office in Town Hall-Rockville, 03/??/80; Topics: Town Government; Landmarks (Box 6, Folder MH.840)
  - Rock. Pub. Hosp. Nursing Assoc.-Mary Lou?-Rockville, 03/??/80; Topics: Rockville Hospital; Civic Organizations (Box 6, Folder MH.841)
  - Carl F. Sternat-Vernon, 01/??/80; Names: Carl F. Sternat (Box 6, Folder MH.841A)
  - Lake St School students design poster for "Year of the Child"-Vernon, 3/28/1980; Topics: Schools & Education (Box 6, Folder MH.842)
  - Miss Tolland County Contest-Vernon, 04/??/80; Topics: Social Organizations (Box 6, Folder MH.843)
  - Ursula Luetjen & Lew Stein-Vernon, 4/3/1980; Names: Ursula Luetjen & Lew Stein (Box 6, Folder MH.844)
  - Rabbitt Run-Rockville, 4/7/1980; Topics: Recreation (Box 6, Folder MH.845)
  - Phone Book Fundraiser for Playscape-Delivery-Rockville, 4/14/1980; Topics: Schools & Education (Box 6, Folder MH.846)